Guide to the E. Raymond Hall Collection
University of Kansas
- PP 169
  - (Box Box 11)
    - Rock Creek Park (Folder 43)
    - Rockwood National Camp at the Nation's Capital (Folder 44)
    - The Rockefeller Foundation: A review for 1946 (Folder 45)
    - Russell Cave National Monument, Alabama (Folder 46)
    - Rocky Mountain National Park, Colorado (Folder 47-51)
    - Richmond National Battlefield Park, Virginia (Folder 52-54)
    - Rainbow Bridge National Monument, Utah (Folder 55-57)
    - Miscellaneous "S" (Folder 58-59)
    - Scotts Bluff National Monument, Nebraska (Folder 60)
    - Sartoga National Historic Park, New York (Folder 61-64)
    - San Juan National Historic Site, Puerto Rico (Folder 65-67)
    - Saguaro National Monument, Arizona (Folder 68-70)
    - Sunset Crater National Monument, Arizona (Folder 71)
    - Stones River National Battlefield, Tennessee (Folder 72)
    - Statue of Liberty National Monument, New York (Folder 73-74)
    - St. Croix, United States Virgin Islands (Folder 75)
    - Sitka National Monument, Alaska (Folder 76)
    - Shiloh National Military Park, Tennessee (Folder 77)
    - Shenandoah National Park, Virginia (Folder 78-80)
    - Shadow Mountain National Recreation Area, Colorado (Folder 81)
    - Sequoia and Kings Canyon National Parks, California (Folder 82-85)
    - Salem Maritime National Historic Site, Massachusetts (Folder 86)
    - Sagamore Hill National Historic Site, New York (Folder 87)
    - Miscellaneous "T" (Folder 88)
    - Tumacacori National Monument, Arizona (Folder 89)
    - Theodore Roosevelt Island, Washington D.C. (Folder 90)
    - Theodore Roosevelt Birthplace, New York (Folder 91)
    - Tupelo National Battlefiled, Mississippi (Folder 92)
    - Tuzigoot National Monument, Arizona (Folder 93-94)
    - Touro Synagogue National Historic Site, Rhode Island (Folder 95)
    - Tonto National Monument (Folder 96)
    - Timpanogos Cave National Monument, Utah (Folder 97)
    - Thomas Jefferson Memorial, Washington, D.C. (Folder 98)
    - Theodore Roosevelt National Memorial Park, North Dakota (Folder 99-101)
    - The United States Marine Corps War Memorial, Washington, D.C. (Folder 102)
    - Bureau of Land Management, Utah (Folder 103)
    - Vanderbilt Mansion National Historic Site, New York (Folder 104-106)
    - Vicksburg National Military Park, Mississippi (Folder 107-108)
    - Virgin Islands National Park, Virgin Islands (Folder 109-112)
    - Washington, D.C. (Folder 113-115)
    - The White House (Folder 116)
    - Wupatki and Sunset Crater, Arizona (Folder 117)
  - (Box Box 12)
    - Wright Brothers National Memorial, North Carolina (Folder 1-3)
    - Wind Cave National Park, South Dakota (Folder 4-5)
    - Whitman Mission National Site, Washington (Folder 6-7)
    - White Sands National Monument, New Mexico (Folder 8-9)
    - Washington Monument, Washington, D.C. (Folder 10)
    - Whiskeytown Lake, California (Folder 11)
    - Walnut Canyon National Monument, Arizona (Folder 12)
    - Yellowstone National Park, Wyoming, Montana, Idaho (Folder 13-16)
    - Yorktown Battlefield Historical Park, Virginia (Folder 17-18)
    - Yosemite National Park, California (Folder 19-22)
    - Zion National Park, Utah (Folder 23-25)
    - Publications, pamphlets, newsletters, 1971-1972 (Folder 26-42)
    - United States Department of the Interior - memorandums, 1972-1974 (Folder 43-46)
    - Department of the Interior news release, 1972-1974 (Folder 47-58)
    - National Park Service newsletters, 1972-1974 (Folder 59-68)
    - National Parks - The Environmental Journal, March 1971 (Folder 69-71)
    - Wilderness Hearing, The Wilderness Society (Folder 72)
    - List of pages (Folder 73-84)
  - (Box Box 13)
    - Final Report of the President and the Congress of the National Parks Centennial Commission - Washington, D.C. (Folder 1)
    - "Landscapes of Alaska: Their Geologic Evolution" Edited by Howel Williams (Folder 2)
    - The Steamboat Bertrand: History, Excavation, and Architecture (Folder 3)
    - Administrative Policies for Historical Areas of the National Park system (Folder 4)
    - Part one of the National Park System plan history (Folder 5)
    - "Prospectus for a North Cascades National Park" North Cascades Conservation Council, 1963 (Folder 6)
    - A report by the advisory committee to the National Park Service on research (Folder 7)
    - A gathering of nations; A time of purpose, Yellowstone and Grand Teton National Parks, 1972 (Folder 8)
    - "In touch with people: United States Department of the Interior Conservation Yearbook Series No. 9, 1973" (Folder 9)
    - Yellowstone National Park: Its exploration and establishment (Folder 10)
    - In Touch magazine, 1980-1981 (Folder 11-12)
    - "11593" - Heritage Coservation and Recreation Service newsletter (Folder 13)
    - Cultural Resources Management bulletin, 1980-1981 (Folder 14-15)
    - National Park Service news release (Folder 16)
    - Department of the Interior news release, 1980-1981 (Folder 17-18)
    - National Park Service editorial briefs, 1979-1981 (Folder 19-25)
    - Courier: The National Park Service Newsletter, 1980-1981 (Folder 26-30)
    - United States Department of the Interior memorandums, 1980-1981 (Folder 31-36)
    - Publications, bulletins, newsletters (Folder 37-42)
    - National Park Service brochures (Folder 43-50)
    - Scrapbook (Book 1)
  - (Box Box 14)
    - 11593 - Information related to responsibilities of the Secretary of the Interior, 1979 (Folder 1-2)
    - In Touch - Interpreters Information Exchange, 1978-1980 (Folder 3-5)
    - Courier: The National Park Service Newsletter, 1978-1980 (Folder 6-13)
    - Department of the Interior news release, 1978-1980 (Folder 14-17)
    - National Park Service news release, 1978-1980 (Folder 18-19)
    - National Parks Service editorial briefs, 1978-1980 (Folder 20-28)
    - Redwood National Park (Folder 29-31)
    - National Parks and Conservation magazine (Folder 32-33)
    - CRM Bulletin: Cultural Resoruces Management, 1978-1979 (Folder 34-35)
    - Friends of the Boundary Waters Wilderness newsletter (Folder 36)
    - United States Department of the Interior memorandums, 1978-1980 (Folder 37-44)
    - Recycling Historic Railroad stations: A citizen's manual (Folder 45)
    - Rehabilitation: Fairmount Waterworks, 1978 (Folder 46)
    - Rehabilitation: Danville, 1978 (Folder 47)
    - Rehabilitation: Claremont, 1978 (Folder 48)
    - Publications, pamphlets, bulletins, newsletters (Folder 49-53)
    - The Preservation of Natural Diversity: A Survey and Recommendations, The Nature Conservancy (Folder 54)
    - Big Thicket National Preserve, Texas, Wilderness Study, July 1979 (Folder 55)
    - Grand Canyon National Park, Arizona, final environmental statement (Folder 56)
    - Fire Island National Seashore, New York, Wilderness Study / Preliminary Wilderness Proposal (Folder 57)
    - Cleveland: An Inventory of Historic Engineering and Industrial Sites (Folder 58)
    - The Upper Peninsula of Michigan: An Inventory of Historic Engineering and Industrial Sites (Folder 59)
    - Grand Canyon National Park, Arizona, draft environmental statement (Folder 60)
    - Rhode Island: An Inventory of Historic Engineering and Industrial Sites, Historic American Engineering Record (Folder 61)
    - E. Raymond Hall papers, 1966 (Folder 62-63)
  - (Box Box 15)
    - United States Fish and Wildlife Service, Office of Migratory Bird Management, 1978 (Folder 1-2)
    - Department of the Interior news release, 1976-1978 (Folder 3-7)
    - National Park Service news release, 1976-1978 (Folder 8-12)
    - Courier: The National Park Service newsletter, 1976-1978 (Folder 13-16)
    - Editorial briefs - The National Park Service, 1976-1978 (Folder 17-25)
    - In touch: Interpreters Information Exchange (Folder 26-27)
    - National Park Service newsletter, 1976-1977 (Folder 28-31)
    - Update: Yosemite general management plan, 1977-1978 (Folder 32)
    - Friends of the boundary waters wilderness, 1978 (Folder 33)
    - Preservation briefs, 1978 (Folder 34)
    - 11593 - Information related to responsibilities of the Secretary of the Interior (Folder 35-38)
    - ASC newsletter - Association of Systematics Collections (Folder 39)
    - United States Department of the Interior, 1976-1978 (Folder 40-46)
    - United States Department of the Interior - employment (Folder 47)
    - Technical preservation services reading list, 1977 (Folder 48)
    - Midwest Regional Advisory Committee Meeting, 1977 (Folder 49-51)
    - Publications, bulletins, papers, newsletters (Folder 52-58)
    - National Park Service brochures and publications (Folder 59-63)
    - Mountain Home, 1977 (Folder 64)
    - Index - National Park System and Affiliated Areas, 1977 (Folder 65)
    - Historic American Engineering Record Catalog, 1976 (Folder 66)
    - Fort Stanwix: History, Historic Furnishing, and Historic Structures Reports (Folder 67)
    - "Shenandoah trip", April 20-22, 1959 [empty envelope] (Folder 68)
    - E. Raymond Hall correspondence with the Department of Agriculture, 1924 (Folder 69)
    - Predatroy mammals, hearings before the subcommittee on fisheries and wildlife conservation (Folder 70)
    - Annual Report of the Chief Scientist of the National Park Service, CY 1977 (Book 1)
  - (Box Box 16)
    - Research Foundation of Kansas, 1967 (Folder 1-2)
    - Economic Development for Kansas, 1963 (Folder 3-5)
    - National Research Council - report to the U.S. National Committee for International Biological Program (Folder 6-8)
    - Religion - The Journal of Kansas School of Religion at the University of Kansas (2), 1972 (Folder 9)
    - World's bulletin: Biology, Earth Science and Chemistry (2), 1977 (Folder 10)
    - United States Department of the Interior news release, 1967 (Folder 11-12)
    - United States Department of the Interior (Folder 13)
    - Maps and Atlases: Selected new acquisitions in the map library, University of Kansas Libraries, 1978 (Folder 14)
    - Save-the-Redwoods League (Folder 15-19)
    - Kansas! magazine (Folder 20-24)
    - Conservation Foundation: Letter newsletter (Folder 25-26)
    - Kansas recreation and park association: Focus newsletter, 1975 (Folder 27)
    - 11593 newsletter - National Park Service (Folder 28)
    - A self study: Extension classes and centers at the Univesity of Kansas, 1969 (Folder 29)
    - Research Foundation of Kansas, 1965-1966 (Folder 30)
    - Student handbook 1964-1965, University of Kansas (Folder 31)
    - State of the University, 1965, 1967 (Folder 32)
    - Kansas Alumni, January 1970 (Folder 33)
    - The University of Kansas - "What is a university?", 1965 (Folder 34)
    - Faculty handbook, 1965-1966, The University of Kansas (Folder 35)
    - The University of Kansas 59th annual commencement, June 5, 1967 (Folder 36)
    - The Kansas University Endowment Association, Greater University Fund, annual report, 1964 (Folder 37)
    - Annual Report, The University of Kansas School of Religion, 1972 (Folder 38)
    - Annual Report 1969-1970, University of Kansas Libraries (Folder 39)
    - The University of Kansas financial report, 1968 (Folder 40)
    - The University of Kansas financial report, 1965 (Folder 41)
    - The University of Kansas financial report, 1961 (Folder 42)
    - The University of Kansas financial report, 1960 (Folder 43-44)
    - The University of Kansas financial report, 1959 (Folder 45-46)
    - New Directions for the National Park System: The Proposed Kansas Tallgrass Prairie National Park, 1977 (Folder 47)
    - The Advancement of Science, volume XIV, number 54, Dublin 1957 (Folder 48)
    - Polish Academy of Sciences Institute of Ecology, Report on Scientific Activities for 1971 (Folder 49)
    - Science: The endless frontier, 1945 (Folder 50)
    - Journal of Proceedings and Addresses of the 53rd Annual Conference of the Association of American Universities, 1952 (Folder 51)
    - Publications, bulletins, papers, newsletters (Folder 52-62)
    - Department of the Interior and Related Agencies Appropriations for Fiscal Year 1967 (Book 1)
  - (Box Box 17)
    - Zoology 115, E. Raymond Hall, University of California-Berkeley, Spring 1925 (Folder 1)
    - Palaeontology 104A, E. Raymond Hall, University of California-Berkeley, Fall 1924 (Folder 2)
    - Palaeontology 106, E. Raymond Hall, University of California-Berkeley, Fall 1924 (Folder 3)
    - Zoology 110, E. Raymond Hall, University of California-Berkeley (Folder 4)
    - Zoology-Experimental Zoology, E. Raymond Hall, [University of California-Berkeley], Fall of 1925 (Folder 5)
    - Palaeontology 104A, book II, E. Raymond Hall, University of California-Berkeley, Fall 1924 (Folder 6)
    - Palaeontology 104B, book I, E. Raymond Hall, University of California-Berkeley, Spring 1925 (Folder 7)
    - Palaeontology 106C, E. Raymond Hall, University of California-Berkeley, Fall 1924 (Folder 8)
    - Loose notes, E. Raymond Hall, University of California-Berkeley, Fall 1924 (Folder 9-10)
    - Field book notes (Folder 11)
    - Information on mammals (Folder 12)
    - Defenders of Wildlife (Folder 13-51)
    - Reorganization and chairman of zool[ogy] 116-113 (Folder 52-53)
    - Zool[ogy] 116 (Folder 54-58)
    - zool[ogy] 113 (Folder 59-65)
    - University of Kansas, graduate student information, 1939-1940 (Folder 66)
  - (Box Box 18)
    - A request by the people of Kansas for the creation of a tallgrass prairie national park in Kansas, 1971 (Folder 1)
    - Saving the prairie two days at a time (Folder 2)
    - American Society of Zoologists (Folder 3)
    - Endangered plants and animals of Oregon, 1969 (Folder 4)
    - Fulbright Alumni Association (Folder 5-6)
    - California Academy of Sciences (Folder 7-9)
    - KWRB (Kansas Water Resources Board) newsletter (Folder 10)
    - The Nature Conservancy News, 1978-1979 (Folder 11-14)
    - Kansas! magazine, 1978-1979 (Folder 15-19)
    - Research monitor news, 1978 (Folder 20)
    - NRDC newsletter, Natural Resources Defense Council, 1978 (Folder 21)
    - Outdoor News Bulletin, Wildlife Management Institute, 1979 (Folder 22-27)
    - Conservation Foundation - Letter, 1979 (Folder 28-29)
    - Save-the-Redwoods League, 1979 (Folder 30)
    - Environmental Protection Agency, 1978-1979 (Folder 31)
    - Environmental Policy Center, 1979 (Folder 32)
    - EPA [Environmental Protection Agency] News, 1979 (Folder 33)
    - American Society of Mammalogists, 1978-1979 (Folder 34-35)
    - Publications, pamphlets, bulletins, papers, newsletters (Folder 36-46)
  - (Box Box 19)
    - Final Environmental Impact Statement: General Management Plan, Yosemite National Park, California (Book 1)
  - (Box Box 20)
    - Ministry of Agriculture, State Meteorological Service, Mean and Extreme Meteorological Bulletin, Ankara, 1967 (Book 1)
    - Yosemite: Summary of the Draft General Management Plan (Book 2)
    - The Kansas Sportsman [removed from Box 18] (Book 3)
    - Miscellaneous materials removed from Box 17 (Book 4)
    - Scrapbook: Loose newspaper articles [removed from Box 13] (Book 5)
    - Defenders of Wildlife [2 newspaper clippings] (Book 6)
    - Information on mammals [newspaper articles] (Book 7)
    - National Parks [newspapers clippings removed from Box 7] (Book 8)
    - Newspaper clippings [removed from Box 5] (Book 9)
    - Turkey: brochures, publications, reports [newspaper clippings] (Book 10)
  - (Folder Oversized Folder)
    - Department of the Interior and National Park Service [4 maps]; Turkey: brochures, publications, reports [2 maps] (Folder 1)
- PP 513
  - (Box Box 1)
    - Hillsdale Resevoir (Folder 1)
    - Hillsdale Resevoir (Folder 2)
    - Handwritten manuscript - correspondence (Folder 3)
    - Handwritten manuscript - correspondence (Folder 4)
    - Hillside Resevoir (Folder 5)
    - Racial and subspecific differences in Homosapien (Folder 6)
    - 1949 fish and game bill transcript - correspondence (Folder 7)
    - Correspondence up to 1948 (Folder 8)
    - Correspondence up to 1948 (Folder 9)
    - Correspondence up to 1948 (Folder 10)
    - Correspondence up to 1948 (Folder 11)
    - Correspondence up to 1948 (Folder 12)
    - 87th - 1982 National Park System Advisory Board (Folder 13)
    - Biographical data (Folder 14)
    - C-Ci (1983), Cl-Cle (1983) - correspondence (Folder 15)
    - Jerry Choate 1983 - correspondence (Folder 16)
    - Correspondence 1983 - D-E, Mtg Mns [meeting minutes] 1983, National Park System Advisory Board (Folder 17)
    - Frank Masland 1983 - correspondence (Folder 18)
    - Ma - Mc 1983 - correspondence, Eleanor Lohmann - 1974-[19]75 (Folder 19)
    - F. Robert Henderson 1983 - J-K correspondence (Folder 20)
    - Li-Le, Li-Ly, 1983 - correspondence (Folder 21)
    - Am-Ax 1983 - correspondence (Folder 22)
    - American Society of Mammalogists 1983 - Directory of Members 1978 (Folder 23)
    - Black-footed Ferret - South Dakota (1964) by Richard L. Adrian (Folder 24)
    - B-Bl 1983-, Bo-Bw 1983-, petition 1976 (Folder 25)
    - Correspondence H - 1983 affidavit (Folder 26)
    - Correspondence R - 1978, B - 1982, misc[ellaneous] (Folder 27)
    - Correspondence D - 1982, H-Hi - 1983- (Folder 28)
    - Correspondence N - 1983, US Dept[artment] of Interior NPSAB [National Park Service Advisory Board] (Folder 29)
    - G 1983 - correspondence (Folder 30)
    - Ho-Hy 1983 - correspondence (Folder 31)
    - Correspondence 1983 - P (Folder 32)
    - Correspondence 1983 - F (Folder 33)
    - Kaibab (Folder 34)
    - Letters - Senator Nelson's herbicides and wildlife bill (Folder 35)
  - (Box Box 2)
    - 315 Hillsdale Resevoir, 316 Hillsdale Resevoir (Folder 1)
    - MVZ [museum of vertebrate zoology] notices and memos, Senate hearings 1976, outlines, correspondence (Folder 2)
    - General statement, schedule of curatorial duties, museum related memos (Folder 3)
    - Museum problems, memos, suggestions, assignment of work tablet (Folder 4)
    - Museum duties correspondence, memos, vertebrate review (Folder 5)
    - Plat of MVZ [museum of vertebrate zoology] research space directory, museum of vertebrate zoology (Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - Museum of Vertebrate Zoology (Folder 7)
    - Proceedings, Two new meadow mice, A new pocket gopher, No need for Hillsdale Dam, Natural History 1972 (Folder 8)
    - Foreward, Native mammals, Tallgrass prairie, Hearings (Folder 9)
    - Dallas Natural Science Association quarterly, pesticides not required, commencement schedule hearings (Folder 10)
    - Alternative proposed for Hillsdale, Osawatomie graphic news, Feasible alternative for Hillsdale Resevoir (Folder 11)
    - Prairie National Park, State of biological survey of Kansas (Folder 12)
    - Minutes of the biological faculties (Folder 13)
    - 4065-703 NSF [National Science Foundation], NA [North American] mammals (Folder 14)
    - 4360-705 Navy, Zoogeog. and System., Y379 - 703 (NSF) [National Science Foundation] Ha. Sys. Rec. Amer. Ursus. (Folder 15)
    - 3591 - 5038, Bears ursus., 3823-5038 (Folder 16)
    - GB 30969 4830 Bio. - Med., 4852-5706 (Folder 17)
    - KU Endowment 4830-X703 (Folder 18)
    - ERH Rice Woodland, Biological Sciences (Folder 19)
    - Wall woods endowment (continued), biological services (Folder 20)
    - Budget correspondence (Folder 21)
    - Kaibab investigate committee hearings (Folder 22)
    - Correspondence - Deer of California (Folder 23)
    - Correspondence J. Grinnell, conservation matters (Folder 24)
    - Report to President, UC, Martens study, Beaver study (Folder 25)
    - Bubonic plague, 9 publications (Folder 26)
    - Correspondence (Folder 27)
    - Correspondence (Folder 28)
    - Correspondence (Folder 29)
    - Correspondence A-B (Folder 30)
    - Correspondence C-D (Folder 31)
    - Correspondence E-G (Folder 32)
    - Correspondence H (Folder 33)
    - Correspondence I-J-K (Folder 34)
    - Correspondence L (Folder 35)
    - Correspondence M (Folder 36)
    - Correspondence N-O (Folder 37)
    - Correspondence R (Folder 38)
    - Correspondence T-U-V (Folder 39)
    - Correspondence Amer[ican] Society of Mammalogists 1955, E.R. Hall photo by Jim Tice Oct[ober] 1960 [photographs] (Folder 40)
    - Czecheslovakia Sept[ember] 1960 [photographs] (Folder 41)
    - National Conv[ention] of Mammalogists, June 1940, Feb[ruary] 1952 Two Amsden Brothers and Hall [photographs] (Folder 42)
    - E.R. Hall Autumn of 1967, 2 copies photo [photographs] (Folder 43)
    - E.R. Hall Autumn 1967, 2 copies photo [photographs] (Folder 44)
    - E.R. Hall Autumn 1967, 1960 photo by Guy James Tice, Mammal Division of Nat[ural] Hist[ory] Mus[eum] [photographs] (Folder 45)
    - To Dr. E.R. Hall, with my compliments, W.L. Jellison 1947, Dec[ember] 1944, Le Loup, Franklin Co[unty], coyote hunters [photographs] (Folder 46)
    - 1949 fish and game bill transcript - correspondence [photographs] (Folder 47)
    - Chemistry lecture from July 1958, London zoology Feb[ruary] 1951 [photographs] (Folder 48)
    - 37th Annual Mtg [meeting] 1957, American Society of Mammalogists, Advisory Board to the Virgin Islands [photographs] (Folder 49)
    - 66th Stated Meeting Ornithologist's Union, 20th Annual Mtg. [meeting] as Mammalogists [photographs] (Folder 50)
    - Ecology Symposium April 1955, 1956 Mammal meeting [photographs] (Folder 51)
    - 1957 Renel Lipman, Charles A Leone 1948, Cpt. [captain] James E. Cohn, From Louise Kellogg 1950, Mammalogists Faculty Club 1956 [photographs] (Folder 52)
    - 1953 Frankfort (Main) Germany, To Prof[essor] Hall from Albert Sobel, unidentified men (2), March 1950 Matamoros Tamoulifas [photographs] (Folder 53)
    - March 1950, Matamoros, Photos by Curt von Wedel and Alfredo Arnez Cua, unidentified man [photographs] (Folder 54)
    - Chantilly France 1948, Boschma Toller and Hall, unidentified woman, Mrs. Hall? [photographs] (Folder 55)
    - Unidentified woman (Mrs. Hall?), 1959 commencement time, 1958 British Commonwealth vice chancellor, two unidentified women n[o] d[ate] [photographs] (Folder 56)
    - 1941 W.E. Saunder, 1961 Mammalogists symposium, Czechoslovakia [photosgraphs] (Folder 57)
    - Negatives (35mm) of Mrs. Hall's, From early October 1969, Taken by Barry L Siler, Hillsdale Resevoir (Folder 58)
  - (Box Box 3)
    - Correspondence A-B, 1930s-[19]40s (Folder 1-6)
    - Correspondence C-F, 1940s (Folder 7-9)
    - Correspondence G-H, 1940s (Folder 10-14)
    - Correspondence L-M, U-Z, 1940s (Folder 15-20)
    - Correspondence N-R, 1940s (Folder 21-24)
    - Correspondence S-W, 1940s (Folder 25-27)
  - (Box Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, reports, notes, publications (Folder 1)
    - Bldg. [building], campus, "To answer" (Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence (Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous maps, correspondence, publications, memorandum (Folder 4)
    - Navy project (correspondence) (Folder 5)
    - Research note cards, research articles, Department of the Interior memos (Folder 6)
    - Memorandum and correspondence - E. Raymond Hall and the University of Kansas and KU Natural History Museum (Folder 7)
    - National Park Services newsletters, miscellaneous notes, correspondence, writings (Folder 8)
    - National Park Services newsletters, miscellaneous notes, correspondence, writings (Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous publications, correspondence, research, newspaper articles (Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous research notes, correspondence, Department of the Interior newsletters (Folder 11)
    - Notes on rules for mss [manuscript] preparation (Folder 12)
    - Notes mainly from 1922-[19]23 at KU, Carly mss [manuscripts] of birds of Douglas County (Folder 13)
    - Pyramid Lake notes summer 1924 (Folder 14)
    - Nebraska field expedition summer 1922 (Folder 15)
    - Correspondence - old mss [manuscripts] (Folder 16)
    - Manuscripts - possibly to finish (Folder 17)
    - Staff mtg. [meeting] minutes, course materials, notes (Folder 18)